Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.05, 16 fragments 07 x 5.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.06, 16 fragments 13 x 6.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.07, 16 fragments 02.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.08, 16 fragments 05 x 4.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.09, 16 fragments 07.5 x 3 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.10, 16 fragments 06.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.11, 16 fragments 04.5 x 4 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.12, 16 fragments 02 x 3 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.13, 16 fragments 04 x 3 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.14, 16 fragments 08 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.15, 16 fragments 05 x 4.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0535.16, 16 fragments 03.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0535.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.01, 19 fragments 08.2 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.02, 19 fragments 12.5 x 2 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.03, 19 fragments 04.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.04, 19 fragments 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.05, 19 fragments 03.5 x 1 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.06, 19 fragments 08 x 6.5 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.07, 19 fragments 09 x 6 cm (Box 11, Item P.NYU inv 0536.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.08, 19 fragments 05.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.09, 19 fragments 07 x 1.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.10, 19 fragments 03.5 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.11, 19 fragments 03 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.12, 19 fragments 05.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.13, 19 fragments 02 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.14, 19 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.15, 19 fragments 07.5 x 11.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.17, 19 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.18, 19 fragments 02 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0536.19, 19 fragments 02.5 x 00.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0536.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.01, 35 fragments 07 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.02, 35 fragments 04 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.03, 35 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.05, 35 fragments 04 x 10.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.06, 35 fragments 07 x 5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.07, 35 fragments 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.08, 35 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.09, 35 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.10, 35 fragments 06.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.11, 35 fragments 06.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.12, 35 fragments 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.13, 35 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.14, 35 fragments 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.15, 35 fragments 06.5 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.16, 35 fragments 09.5 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.17, 35 fragments 03 x 0.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.18, 35 fragments 08 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.19, 35 fragments 03.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.20, 35 fragments 04 x 4 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.20)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.21, 35 fragments 06.5 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.21)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.22, 35 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.22)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.23, 35 fragments 02.5 x 4 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.23)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.24, 35 fragments 05 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.24)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.25, 35 fragments 02.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.25)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.26, 35 fragments 04.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.26)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.27, 35 fragments 03.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.27)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.28, 35 fragments 03.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.28)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.29, 35 fragments 03.5 x 04 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.29)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.30, 35 fragments 06 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.30)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.31, 35 fragments 05.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.31)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.32, 35 fragments 01.5 x 1 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.32)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.33, 35 fragments 04.5 x 4 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.33)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.34, 35 fragments 04 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.34)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0537.35, 35 fragments 05.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0537.35)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.01, 33 fragments 05.5 x 6 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.02, 33 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.03, 33 fragments 02.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.04, 33 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.05, 33 fragments 02 x 3.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.06, 33 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.07, 33 fragments 02.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.08, 33 fragments 03.5 x 4 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.09, 33 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.10, 33 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.11, 33 fragments 04.5 x 5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.12, 33 fragments 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.13, 33 fragments 02 x 2 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.14, 33 fragments 01.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.15, 33 fragments 09.5 x 17.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.17, 33 fragments 06.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 12, Item P.NYU inv 0538.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.18, 33 fragments 02 x 0.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.19, 33 fragments 03 x 4.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.20, 33 fragments 11.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.20)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.21, 33 fragments 02.5 x 1 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.21)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.22, 33 fragments 02.5 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.22)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.23, 33 fragments 04.5 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.23)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.24, 33 fragments 02 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.24)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.25, 33 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.25)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.26, 33 fragments 02.5 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.26)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.27, 33 fragments 01 x 6 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.27)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.28, 33 fragments 02.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.28)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.29, 33 fragments 03 x 2.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.29)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.30, 33 fragments 03.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.30)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.31, 33 fragments 06 x 9 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.31)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.32, 33 fragments 03 x 1 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.32)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0538.33, 33 fragments 04.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0538.33)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.01, 19 fragments 11.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.02, 19 fragments 07.5 x 5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.03, 19 fragments 02.5 x 9.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.05, 19 fragments 10 x 10 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.07, 19 fragments 02.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.08, 19 fragments 01.5 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.10, 19 fragments 01 x 5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.11, 19 fragments 01.5 x 7 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.12, 19 fragments 03 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.15, 19 fragments 06 x 6.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.16, 19 fragments 07.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.17, 19 fragments 06 x 4.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.18, 19 fragments 06 x 6 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0539.19, 19 fragments 06.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0539.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.01, 18 fragments 07.5 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.02, 18 fragments 2.5 x 12 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.03, 18 fragments 06 x 5.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.04, 18 fragments 00.5 x 0.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.05, 18 fragments 05.5 x 2 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.06, 18 fragments 11.5 x 6 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.07, 18 fragments 02 x 6.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.08, 18 fragments 05 x 4.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.09, 18 fragments 01 x 4.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.10, 18 fragments 03 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.11, 18 fragments 04 x 7 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.12, 18 fragments 02 x 1 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.13, 18 fragments 03.5 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.14, 18 fragments 04 x 2 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.15, 18 fragments 03 x 6.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.16, 18 fragments 03.5 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.17, 18 fragments 04 x 10.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0540.18, 18 fragments 05 x 6 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0540.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.01, 19 fragments 08 x 3.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.02, 19 fragments 03.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.03, 19 fragments 03 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.04, 19 fragments 06 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.05, 19 fragments 06 x 4 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.06, 19 fragments 04 x 3.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.07, 19 fragments 09 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.08, 19 fragments 04.5 x 6 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.09, 19 fragments 02.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.10, 19 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.11, 19 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.12, 19 fragments 06.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 13, Item P.NYU inv 0541.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.13, 19 fragments 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0541.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.14, 19 fragments 03.5 x 6 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0541.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.15, 19 fragments 08 x 3 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0541.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.16, 19 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0541.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.17, 19 fragments 02 x 4 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0541.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.18, 19 fragments 03.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0541.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0541.19, 19 fragments 10.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0541.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.01, 34 fragments 06 x 05 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.02, 34 fragments 07.5 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.03, 34 fragments 01.5 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.04, 34 fragments 04.5 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.05, 34 fragments 03 x 4.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.06, 34 fragments 05.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.07, 34 fragments 07 x 2.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.08, 34 fragments 02.5 x 6.6 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.09, 34 fragments 02 x 2.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.10, 34 fragments 01 x 4 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.11, 34 fragments 03.5 x 3 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.12, 34 fragments 03 x 1 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.13, 34 fragments 07.0 x 02.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.14, 34 fragments 04 x 3.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.15, 34 fragments 02 x 3.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.16, 34 fragments 02.5 x 5.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.17, 34 fragments 01.5 x 1 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.18, 34 fragments 02 x 1.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.19, 34 fragments 04 x 3 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.20, 34 fragments 03.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.20)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.21, 34 fragments 03.5 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.21)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.22, 34 fragments 02 x 1 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.22)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.23, 34 fragments 02.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.23)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.24, 34 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.24)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.25, 34 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.25)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.26, 34 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.26)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.27, 34 fragments 05 x 4 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.27)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.28, 34 fragments 03 x 1.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.28)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.29, 34 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.29)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.30, 34 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.30)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.31, 34 fragments 0.5 x 9 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.31)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.32, 34 fragments 02 x 1.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.32)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.33, 34 fragments 04.5 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.33)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0542.34, 34 fragments 04.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0542.34)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.01, 27 fragments 03.5 x 13 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.02, 27 fragments 02 x 11.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.03, 27 fragments 09 x 3.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.04, 27 fragments 05 x 3 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.05, 27 fragments 03.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.06, 27 fragments 01.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.07, 27 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.08, 27 fragments 01.5 x 2.2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.09, 27 fragments 01.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.10, 27 fragments 05 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.11, 27 fragments 02.5 x 4 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.12, 27 fragments 03 x 3.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.13, 27 fragments 02.5 x 5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.14, 27 fragments 05.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.15, 27 fragments 03.5 x 3 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.16, 27 fragments 08 x 4.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.17, 27 fragments 02.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.18, 27 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.19, 27 fragments 02.5 x 7 cm (Box 14, Item P.NYU inv 0543.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.20, 27 fragments 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0543.20)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.21, 27 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0543.21)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.22, 27 fragments 02 x 6 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0543.22)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.23, 27 fragments 08.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0543.23)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.24, 27 fragments 01.5 x 3 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0543.24)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.25, 27 fragments 07.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0543.25)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.26, 27 fragments 06.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0543.26)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0543.27, 27 fragments 01.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0543.27)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.01, 26 fragments 02.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.02, 26 fragments 08.5 x 4 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.03, 26 fragments 01.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.04, 26 fragments 04 x 3 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.05, 26 fragments 02 x 6 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.06, 26 fragments 04 x 3 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.07, 26 fragments 05 x 2.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.08, 26 fragments 02.5 x 7 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.09, 26 fragments 02 x 6.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.10, 26 fragments 04 x 2 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.11, 26 fragments 01 x 3 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.12, 26 fragments 02 x 3 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.13, 26 fragments 03.5 x 2 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.14, 26 fragments 03 x 8.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.15, 26 fragments 08.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.16, 26 fragments 04.5 x 5.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.17, 26 fragments 04.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.18, 26 fragments 02 x 4 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.19, 26 fragments 02 x 3 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.20, 26 fragments 01 x 2 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.20)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.21, 26 fragments 05 x 5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.21)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.22, 26 fragments 02.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.22)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.23, 26 fragments 03 x 3 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.23)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.24, 26 fragments 03 x 1 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.24)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.25, 26 fragments 05.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.25)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0544.26, 26 fragments 02 x 4.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0544.26)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.01, 39 fragments 04 x 7.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.02, 39 fragments 03 x 4.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.03, 39 fragments 01.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.04, 39 fragments 07.5 x 7 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.05, 39 fragments 01.5 x 1 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0545.06, 39 fragments 02.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 15, Item P.NYU inv 0545.06)